♪Beneath the mask♪
♪Lies another mask♪
(Original Story: Haishi Lisheng)
♪Who's sincere♪
♪Who's only pretending♪
♪Borrowing your light♪
♪I walk through my own night♪
♪You are my weakness♪
♪And my weapon too♪
♪Draped in your shadow♪
♪I walk the blade's edge♪
♪If one day♪
♪The mask shatters♪
♪Will you still♪
♪Recognize my light♪
=The Masked Lover=
(Dashijie, Rongji)
(Presenting the Peerless Duo,)
(Admission by Ticket, Tickets on Sale)
(Lin Kefu, Su Yutang.)
(So beautiful!)
(Lin Kefu)
(The Peerless Duo live up to their name)
(They're gorgeous!)
(Su Yutang)
(In this world,)
(no one is more in sync with me
than Kefu.)
(Offstage, we're sworn sisters.)
(Onstage,)
(we're the perfect magic partners.)
(What's the gun for?)
(Lu Shaoyun)
(Kefu and I)
(are always thinking of each other,)
(always care for each other,)
(and would never hurt each other.)
(Murder!)
(She's bleeding!)
(Su Yutang.)
(Tell us the truth.)
(Why did you kill her?)
You've got it wrong.
I didn't kill her.
(Three Hours Earlier)
It was a magic trick.
A magic trick!
It's all an illusion.
Lin Kefu isn't dead.
(But I never imagined)
(that her curtain call that night)
(would also be Kefu's final curtain.)
I'm heading out.
Where are you going?
I'll get something and be right back.
I got tickets to Magnolia,
your favorite.
Don't be late.
I know.
Go take off your makeup.
I'll be right back.
Wait for me.
I will.
(If Kefu knew)
(I found her late mother's keepsake,)
(she'd be so happy.)
Kefu!
What's wrong?
Who did this?
Somebody, come quick!
Help!
Inspector!
Please save my friend!
(Su Yutang commits arson and murder.)
(Take her away.)
Kefu!
Murder and arson.
Caught red-handed.
There's no denying it.
You've got the wrong person!
I'm a witness.
A witness?
You're just in time.
Whoever has these two items
is Iron Leopard's biological daughter.
(He Jingchen)
She won't do.
Find another.
Why not her?
Her height, age, and looks
all match.
Look at her.
Too timid.
Not quick enough.
With Iron Leopard,
she wouldn't last three days.
I'll find someone more suitable.
Get out.
How many times have I told you?
When you find Iron Leopard's
biological daughter,
tell me at once,
instead of killing her on your own.
But you also said
we couldn't let his real daughter
get a chance to meet him.
I figured
the dead can't cause trouble.
Don't worry.
I left no trace.
No trace?
Someone saw you.
Who?
Who are you?
You said you're a witness.
(He's in military uniform.)
(Is he from the Governor's Residence?)
You saw the killer?
Kefu!
Hang in there.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Yutang.
Listen to me first.
Lu Shaoyun is the killer.
(But Lu Shaoyun)
(is the young master of
the Governor's Residence.)
Tell me the truth.
Who is the killer?
You're from the Governor's Residence.
This doesn't matter.
Let me go!
You're quick.
Not as quick as you.
(I didn't expect a better candidate
to show up so soon.)
Awake?
You're lucky.
Before I came to see you,
I executed a few prisoners at camp.
I ran out of bullets.
(If he wanted to kill me to silence me,)
(he wouldn't go to all this trouble.)
(Since he brought me here,)
(I still have a chance.)
So, are you going to shoot me again?
You still haven't named the killer.
(I can't tell him.)
(With people from the
Governor's Residence here,)
(I can't accuse one of their own)
(and expect to live.)
I didn't get a good look.
I only saw the killer from behind.
You didn't get a good look?
That puts the police in a bind.
But Lin Kefu was murdered.
And I didn't do it.
The police can't accuse a good person.
Is that so?
The police need to close the case.
If she was murdered,
someone has to be the killer.
I can give you a chance.
What chance?
A chance to be a good person.
I ask. You answer.
Answer well,
and you might live to be one.
How did Lin Kefu die?
(He's right.)
(If I insist she was murdered,)
(there has to be a killer.)
(If they protect the real killer,)
(they'll pin it on me.)
Was she murdered?
No one killed Lin Kefu.
She died in the fire.
Quick thinking.
But won't that weigh on your conscience?
But the theater can only have one
head magician.
You want to be head magician?
Of course.
I'm better at magic than she was.
Now that she's dead,
this is my chance.
Why do you want to be head magician?
For the money.
Good. Money makes things easy.
Now you have two choices.
One.
The police perform an autopsy.
Cause of death: homicide.
You envied Lin Kefu's position
as head magician.
You're the prime suspect.
And you were caught red-handed.
Two.
She died in the fire.
From then on,
you'll have more money
than you can spend.
So...
you decide what goes
in the autopsy report.
Looks like I only have one choice.
I'll take that as your answer.
But before that,
I need you to help me
pull off a magic trick.
And we'll need a different stage.
Where's the new stage?
The Governor's Residence.
The Governor's Residence?
You want me to perform magic there?
I want you to become the young lady
of the Governor's Residence.
I see.
It's Kefu.
She's the governor's real daughter.
After tonight,
you'll be the real young lady of
the Governor's Residence.
(Why dispose of his real daughter's body
and erase all traces?)
(Then find someone to replace her?)
But no magic trick is ever done alone.
I can be your assistant.
But before that,
I need to take something from you.
What?
Your weakness.
I have nothing.
What weakness could I have?
The Governor's biological daughter
was born with a butterfly birthmark
on her left shoulder.
Now you know your weakness.
Turn around.
♪A lie carved deep into the heart♪
(Loyalty Eternal)
♪Blades clash, leaving us both trapped♪
♪Nightmares from days gone by♪
♪Love and hate intertwine♪
♪In eyes ignited by sparks♪
♪Each blooming with a fierce edge♪
♪Shattering moonlight on the ground♪
♪I look up and meet your gaze♪
♪Unveiling all the absurdity♪
♪Seeking love's only truth♪
♪Through fate's layered maze♪
♪Charging toward the unknown♪
♪Don't forget your stubborn heart♪
♪Fire tempers the strength to go on♪
♪Counting down the long night's haze♪
♪With my own hands, I draw the dawn♪
♪Boundless♪